<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/4.3.1" created="2015-09-22 20:19" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>Semona Blogs Demo</title>
	<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com</link>
	<description>Just another Semona Demo site</description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 20:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://semona.wpengine.com/</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>3</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>semona</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>theme.paradise14@gmail.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[semona]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.3.1</generator>

	<item>
		<title>A 3-Step Plan for Finding and Buying Your Next Home</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/a-3-step-plan-for-finding-and-buying-your-next-home/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=146</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Chances are you’ve considered buying a home — maybe you even attended a couple of open houses and ran the numbers. But once you get serious, there are a few points you need to consider before signing a contract and heading to your closing.

Buying a home takes more time and research than, say, buying a tablet or smartphone. Before diving in, it’s important to understand the process. Every home buyer’s journey happens on a slightly different timeline, but here are some steps every prospective buyer should take.

1. Search and discover

The home-buying process often occurs organically, and may begin a year or more before the actual purchase. You’ll get started by viewing home listings online to discover what types of homes you can get in different price ranges.

Look at homes in your favorite neighborhoods, and review statistics and reports on home values. Use this time to dream about some of your favorite home features, and start to put together your list of priorities.

Most buyers will find a property during this phase that prompts them to move to the next stage.

2. Do the math and your required homework

Most would-be home buyers need a mortgage to purchase a home. While the process has gotten easier as we’ve moved farther away from the financial and lending crisis, it can still be challenging if you’re not prepared.

You need to know what you can afford, the types of loans available and how what you can afford will affect your home search. Pull your credit report, and understand your financial situation. Then you can get pre-approved.

Many buyers need to repair their credit score, save more money or allow cash to season for some time before buying. Use the next few months to address any financial issues.

3. Dive in and have fun

At some point along the way, you should connect with a local real estate agent. These relationships form early, and having that person beside you during your search should be invaluable.

Go to open houses, make appointments and see as many homes as possible. Before making an offer, you’ll need to know the market inside and out. The more homes you see, the more you will know about your local real estate market, and the more confidence you will have when that dream house comes along.

And if you miss out on a deal or two, it’s okay. It’s all part of the process. Don’t feel rushed, and realize that the home search often becomes a part-time job. Have fun with it.

If you find yourself in the real estate market prior to doing significant research, you may be jumping the gun. Unlike a tablet, smartphone or even a car, a home is a long-term investment — and a special one at that. It’s where your life will happen. Move too quickly and buyer’s remorse can creep in.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>146</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:32:40</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:32:40</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>a-3-step-plan-for-finding-and-buying-your-next-home</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="business"><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[203]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[new-french-perfume-museum-showcases-the-marvels-of-scent-making]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>This terrified little girl just discovered her own shadow</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/this-terrified-little-girl-just-discovered-her-own-shadow/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=148</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Nunc elementum odio dui, et eleifend arcu interdum pulvinar. Donec pulvinar, lectus id ultricies venenatis, nunc diam blandit justo, vitae sollicitudin ligula magna id nibh. Fusce scelerisque eros mollis, sagittis enim in, rhoncus quam. Donec lobortis consequat tristique. Etiam nec tincidunt nibh, vitae commodo enim. Aliquam auctor lectus leo, eget placerat sapien accumsan ut. Pellentesque tortor velit, gravida nec aliquet sed, egestas non urna. Donec auctor varius mollis. Quisque et dictum ligula, eget molestie nisi. Nunc feugiat tellus vitae mi vulputate pretium. Pellentesque gravida venenatis risus, eu sodales lacus dapibus in. Etiam varius, arcu sit amet suscipit rhoncus, nunc tortor lobortis nibh, at imperdiet dolor ipsum eu dolor. Vivamus mollis sapien facilisis felis cursus, ac euismod eros sodales. Ut id tempor mi. Sed et augue ligula. Phasellus elementum mattis felis nec ultricies.

Integer ut neque sit amet nisi bibendum dictum. Integer condimentum, leo sit amet maximus tincidunt, mauris massa dapibus libero, a porttitor purus ex et nisi. Etiam egestas orci et interdum cursus. Morbi in gravida lectus, quis eleifend arcu. Pellentesque placerat tincidunt blandit. In ac mauris ut ipsum pulvinar consequat. Duis dignissim posuere ligula, vel iaculis nulla pharetra sed. Proin sapien leo, volutpat ac ipsum vel, aliquet tincidunt nulla. Vivamus augue erat, dapibus sed nisi vitae, sagittis placerat mauris. Maecenas et est lobortis, bibendum arcu sed, ullamcorper massa. Sed non ipsum imperdiet justo gravida hendrerit vel et ipsum.

Donec elementum diam quis tellus tincidunt sagittis. Ut et placerat urna. Vestibulum vitae felis gravida, pretium magna sit amet, aliquet risus. Curabitur hendrerit sem ullamcorper, sodales felis et, ultrices justo. Ut venenatis enim sed lacus tempor, ut rutrum ante pharetra. Sed sodales laoreet justo et auctor. Mauris ullamcorper non ante vitae cursus. Etiam placerat metus vitae erat vehicula convallis. Etiam scelerisque ligula ut lorem consequat rutrum. Cras sed ornare ligula, ac tincidunt nulla. In dictum odio vitae varius dignissim. Morbi elementum erat ut mattis imperdiet. Maecenas ut varius velit. Nulla quis viverra nunc. Aenean efficitur metus nibh, at dignissim purus fermentum in. Integer mattis cursus mauris, sed placerat odio feugiat et.

Praesent egestas aliquet blandit. Nam facilisis mattis quam, quis malesuada mi tristique ut. Donec finibus condimentum scelerisque. Nullam sit amet fringilla leo. Mauris aliquet vehicula imperdiet. Suspendisse tortor dui, pulvinar sit amet purus sed, vulputate vulputate nisi. Nulla id sollicitudin ante. Sed id ante aliquam, vestibulum nisl ac, pulvinar dolor. Nam varius massa at gravida molestie. Donec pharetra tortor nec mollis vestibulum. Aenean posuere tempus mauris nec pulvinar. Phasellus gravida feugiat tortor, eu iaculis orci auctor quis. Donec semper suscipit lobortis. Aliquam vitae mi lorem. Proin semper ipsum dolor, non venenatis est aliquam sodales.

Integer faucibus vestibulum sem non suscipit. Integer eu tellus sit amet sapien auctor pellentesque ut et ipsum. Nunc luctus elit id nibh aliquam eleifend. Etiam dictum lectus nisi, a bibendum orci laoreet in. Nullam ullamcorper in sapien accumsan malesuada. Nam nisi diam, placerat vel cursus vel, ornare nec nunc. Integer ut arcu aliquet ex molestie vulputate id vestibulum libero. Sed dapibus sapien non sapien facilisis, vitae hendrerit ex vehicula. Integer nisi diam, lacinia in eleifend eget, rutrum eu justo. Donec sit amet tellus a diam placerat dignissim eget a nulla. Donec egestas libero sed dui facilisis, eget mattis nisi mattis. Cras ligula elit, auctor at lacus quis, placerat feugiat ex. Donec feugiat efficitur dapibus. Donec purus eros, eleifend imperdiet sem id, fermentum pharetra enim. Aenean quam massa, scelerisque sit amet leo sit amet, rutrum faucibus tortor.

Proin ut porttitor ex. In mollis scelerisque risus, id suscipit tellus varius pulvinar. Morbi cursus eget augue sit amet placerat. Pellentesque quis cursus dolor. Suspendisse iaculis dictum scelerisque. Ut non fermentum turpis, vel ornare dui. Praesent nec venenatis risus. Mauris lacus ante, rutrum ac augue id, convallis sagittis massa. Integer maximus dui sed orci varius, eget feugiat leo consequat. Pellentesque sodales diam ex, ac convallis velit vulputate non. Sed blandit tincidunt posuere. Maecenas tempus viverra eros ut eleifend. Sed viverra consectetur sagittis. Morbi faucibus, lorem a pellentesque scelerisque, lacus nunc tempus ex, eu cursus nibh tortor sed ex. Vivamus ante odio, accumsan rhoncus gravida ut, iaculis et massa. Quisque efficitur libero a aliquet malesuada.

Nam eget magna eget nunc dignissim feugiat. Nam non justo a diam scelerisque accumsan. Suspendisse tincidunt libero non vestibulum mattis. In porta et odio vel mattis. Vestibulum rhoncus interdum tempor. Mauris tempus semper tristique. Integer metus ex, ullamcorper vitae consectetur id, semper ac nibh. Praesent dictum tortor sagittis diam sollicitudin, ut lacinia leo laoreet.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>148</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:34:08</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:34:08</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>this-terrified-little-girl-just-discovered-her-own-shadow</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="nature"><![CDATA[Nature]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[202]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>10 PLACES IN ICELAND TO CONNECT WITH EARTH AND NATURE</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/10-places-in-iceland-to-connect-with-earth-and-nature/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=150</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>1. HAUKADALALUR</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/geysir-iceland.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53197" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/geysir-iceland.jpg" alt="Geysir in Iceland " width="800" height="533" /></a>

Part of the Golden Circle in South West Iceland, the geothermal area is quite an attraction. It is home of the famous <strong>Geysir</strong> but you need to be lucky to see it erupt.

However the little brother <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/geysir-haukadalur-iceland/" target="_blank">Strokkur</a> is very active. Its powerful jet of water happens every few minutes, so you have plenty of time to really experience this wonder: the bubble growing and growing followed by the column of water which reaches 15 to 20 meters high, sometimes to 40 meters.
<h3>2. JOKULSARLON BEACH</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/jokulsarlon-beach-iceland.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53198" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/jokulsarlon-beach-iceland.jpg" alt="Jokulsarlon Beach, Iceland" width="800" height="533" /></a>

One of the most touristic spots on the south coast of Iceland is the beautiful lagoon of<strong>Jokulsarlon</strong> where the glacier releases huge icebergs. However most visitors do not cross the road to <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/jokulsarlon-iceberg-beach-iceland/" target="_blank">the black sand beach</a> and miss one of the country’s highlights.

The icebergs actually float through a channel into the sea and are pushed back towards the beach by the tide. You can approach these giant blocks of ice and touch them. Some are white, other black and a few are blue, but all look stunning against the waves and the black sand. Truly a privilege to see this work of nature.
<h3>3. HVERIR</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Hverir-l1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53200" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Hverir-l1.jpg" alt="Hverir, Iceland " width="800" height="533" /></a>

Iceland has many geothermal areas but my favorite is <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/hverir-myvatn-iceland/" target="_blank">Hverir</a> in North Iceland.

You can feel the Earth boiling just under the crust with the powerful gas released from the fumaroles and the mud pools. All this activity is intensified by the bare surrounding landscape and the ground colors and the red of Namafjall, the hill behind.
<h3>4. SIGOLDUGLJUFUR</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/sigoldugljufur-iceland1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53201" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/sigoldugljufur-iceland1.jpg" alt="Sigoldugljufur - Iceland" width="800" height="533" /></a>

Hidden in the Central Highlands, the canyon of <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/sigoldugljufur-off-path-iceland/" target="_blank">Sigoldugljufur</a> is very little known. We ended up there by accident and it was one of those moments where you feel you have reached paradise: nothing around, just you and nature.

As the others kept photographing, I sat there in silence enjoying every curve of the canyon and every small ‘tear’ waterfall. Mother Nature is an artist!
<h3>5. HVERFJALL</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Hverfjall-iceland1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53202" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Hverfjall-iceland1.jpg" alt="Hverfjall - Iceland" width="800" height="533" /></a>

I had seen small volcanic craters before <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/hverfjall-crater-iceland/" target="_blank">Hverfjall</a> in North Iceland, but its size and bare landscape makes it one of a kind.

As I walked the 1km long rim of the 140 meter deep volcano, my mind started traveling back in time 2,800 years ago and imagining the power of the eruption. I felt privileged to see the evidence of such an intense event.
<h3>6. BLUE LAGOON</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/blue-lagoon-iceland1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53203" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/blue-lagoon-iceland1.jpg" alt="The Blue Lagoon - Iceland" width="800" height="600" /></a>

I must admit, contrary to most visitors of Iceland, I am not a big fan of the <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/blue-lagoon-iceland/" target="_blank">Blue Lagoon</a>. And by that I mean the spa and the huge flow of tourists.

The lagoon itself is man-made but the fascinating part is that the geothermal seawater comes from 2,000 meters beneath the surface. It has traveled through porous lava, reaches us at 50°C and ends up at 38°C in the lagoon. Can you imagine it coming from so deep under us?
<h3>7. LEIHRNJUKUR</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/leirhnjuku-Iceland1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53204" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/leirhnjuku-Iceland1.jpg" alt="Leihrnjukur - Iceland" width="800" height="600" /></a>

Imagine walking in a field of fuming lava. Crazy? Well, not that much.

You can actually do it in North Iceland on a walking track around <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/leirhnjukur-iceland/" target="_blank">Leirhnjukur</a> which is still steaming 30 years after the last volcanic event. Of course you have to stay on the path if you do not want your shoes’ soles to melt. But what an adventure!
<h3>8. PSEUDO-CRATERS</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/pseudocraters-iceland1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53205" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/pseudocraters-iceland1.jpg" alt="Pseudo-craters, Iceland" width="800" height="533" /></a>

I know the title says you can connect with Mother Earth, but now it is time to connect with Father Mars. Let me explain.

The <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/myvatn-pseudo-craters-iceland/" target="_blank">pseudo-craters of Lake Myvatn</a> are the result of a rare phenomenon (almost entirely found in Iceland) where water is trapped under lava. But scientists believe the same is happening on planet Mars!
<h3>9. ALDEYJARFOSS</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Aldeyjarfoss-iceland1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53206" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Aldeyjarfoss-iceland1.jpg" alt="Aldeyjarfoss - Iceland" width="800" height="533" /></a>

An off the beaten track waterfall, <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/aldeyjarfoss-warterfall-iceland/" target="_blank">Aldeyjarfoss</a> offers the evidence of both volcanic activity and erosion by the glacial river: the land of fire and ice.

This is a place to appreciate how the powerful flow of water created a passage allowing us to see various shapes of basalt columns from the successive volcanic events.
<h3>10. DIMMUBORGIR</h3>
<a href="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/dimmuborgir-iceland1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-53207" src="http://www.ytravelblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/dimmuborgir-iceland1.jpg" alt="Dimmuborgir - Iceland" width="800" height="533" /></a>

And finally, if you want to sing the jingle ‘Denver, the last dinosaur’ and feel like one could appear any time, I recommend visiting <a href="http://www.zigzagonearth.com/dimmuborgir-iceland/" target="_blank">Dimmuborgir</a> in North Iceland.

Most lava fields are spread but low. This unique one has huge lava formations surrounding you that make you feel like you have traveled in time.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>150</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:35:51</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:35:51</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>10-places-in-iceland-to-connect-with-earth-and-nature</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="nature"><![CDATA[Nature]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="travel"><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[200]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_is_featured</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Children need teachers to teach them - not computers</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/children-need-teachers-to-teach-them-not-computers/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=152</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Walk into any school in term time and you will likely see the kids hard at work on their computers, chatting online, or texting their friends but, according to the OECD, all this technology is not making our kids any smarter. In fact, it says, the evidence suggests it is having the opposite effect.
As the OECD's education director, Andreas Schleicher, points out in his report, Students, Computers and Learning: Making The Connection, published today, although students who use computers "moderately" at school tend to have somewhat better learning outcomes than students who use computers rarely, "students who use computers very frequently at school do a lot worse in most learning outcomes, even after accounting for social background and student demographics".

It gets worse.

"The results also show no appreciable improvements in student achievement in reading, mathematics or science in the countries that had invested heavily in information and communication technology (ICT) for education," said Schleicher. "And perhaps the most disappointing finding is that technology seems of little help in bridging the skills divide between advantaged and disadvantaged students."

Other findings of the report included:

Students get worse results the more frequently they use computers
A little use is a good thing as students who use computers once or twice a week, rather than every day, get better outcomes that those who use them rarely.
The countries that have invested the most in technology show "no appreciable improvements" in reading, mathematics or science, the report says.
High-achieving school systems such as South Korea and Shanghai in China have lower levels of computer use in school.
According to Schleicher, one of the "most disappointing findings" of the report was that "the socio-economic divide between students is not narrowed by technology, perhaps even amplified".

Schleicher's department has undertaken a full analysis into the role that education plays in developing a population with the right skills, and has come up with results that overturn the prevailing wisdom on education.

Computers, he believes, are not much help. "Put simply," he says, "ensuring that every child attains a baseline level of proficiency in reading and mathematics seems to do more to create equal opportunities in a digital world than expanding or subsidising access to high-tech devices and services."

But he also believes that "most parents and teachers" will not be surprised by the finding that students "who spend more than six hours online per weekday outside of school are particularly at risk of reporting that they feel lonely at school".

One interpretation, said Schleicher, is that "building deep, conceptual understanding and higher-order thinking requires intensive teacher-student interactions, and technology sometimes distracts from this valuable human engagement".]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>152</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:37:18</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:37:18</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>children-need-teachers-to-teach-them-not-computers</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="technology"><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[199]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[beyonce-could-be-wearing-intel-ligent-fashion-on-her-next-tour]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Travel is a privilege</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/travel-is-a-privilege/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=154</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Let’s face it: not everyone is able to travel. Whether it’s money, family obligations, or circumstance, travel is out of reach for a large percentage of the world’s population.

In the “quit your job to travel the world” cheerleading that happens so often on travel websites (including this one), we often forget that it’s not easy for everyone.

Years on the road have shown me that for many of us, our inability to travel is part a mindset issue (since we believe travel is expensive, we don’t look for ways to make it cheaper) and part a spending issue (we spend money on things we don’t need).

There are those for whom no mindset change, spending cuts, or budget tips will help them travel — those who are too sick, have parents or children to care for, face great debt, or work three jobs just to make rent.

After all, 2.8 billion people — nearly 40% of the world’s population — survive on less than $2 USD a day! In my home country of the United States, 14% of the population is below the poverty line, 46 million people are on food stamps, many have to work two jobs to get by, and we have a trillion dollars in student debt dragging people down.

Nothing any website can say will magically make travel a reality for those people.

Those of us who do travel are a privileged few.

Whether we quit our jobs to travel the world, spend two months in Europe, or take our kids on a short vacation to Disney World, we get to experience something most people of the world will never get a chance to do.

We overlook that too much. As I’ve started building FLYTE — a foundation to help high schools take economically disadvantaged students on educational trips overseas — I’ve thought a lot about privilege.

I grew up in a predominately white, middle-class town with parents who paid my college tuition. I had a job after college that allowed me to live on my own, take vacations, and still save for my first trip around the world. And, because I speak English, I easily found work teaching English in Thailand, where I could save to extend my travels.

That’s not to say that hard work doesn’t count, but hard work doesn’t exist in a bubble — the circumstances that create the opportunities for hard work to bear fruit are often more important.

I’ve met people of all ages, incomes, abilities, and nationalities on the road. Folks like Don and Alison, who are backpacking the world at 70; Michael, who worked 60-hour weeks at a minimum-wage job; Cory, who travels the world in a wheelchair; Ishwinder, who didn’t let visa restrictions stop him; and countless others.

But even they had circumstances that allowed them to travel — support from family and friends, jobs that allowed for overtime, or other skills. They weren’t barely getting by or on social assistance. They didn’t wonder if they could afford their next meal.

So it’s important to remember that we are some of the lucky ones. We get to do something that others will never be able to do.

We are privileged.

Even if you’ve hitchhiked around the world with no money, worked overseas, cut costs to travel around the world on $10 USD a day, or travel-hacked your way to a first-class ticket, you have the opportunity to do something most people go to sleep only dreaming about. You have the freedom and choice to move about the world in a way most people don’t.

That’s a form of privilege.

It’s important that we never forget or be ungrateful for our opportunity.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>154</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:42:07</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:42:07</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>travel-is-a-privilege</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="quotes"><![CDATA[Quotes]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[198]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[i-tried-13-dating-apps-in-30-days-in-search-of-love]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_is_featured</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Why you should listen to your inner voice</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/why-you-should-listen-to-your-inner-voice/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=156</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[The Voice. You’ve heard people talk about it.

In fact, you hear the voice all the time. Telling you why you shouldn’t do things, why you’re not good enough, reminding you why you should be fearful, or causing you to agonise over your decisions.

The WRONG voice.

It’s not the one I’m talking about today. Nor, The Voice that turns buskers into recording artists (although I do like that Voice)

I’m talking about the inner voice – the voice of truth that is always trying to get you to listen. But you choose the other voice instead – the whiny, doubtful, fearful one. It’s louder and often makes more sense with it’s justifications and reasonings.

Always holding you back.

The true voice doesn’t.

It just speaks and pushes you forward. It doesn’t need to justify or clarify. It commands. But, it’s a peaceful and loving command, not one of an evil dictator.

If you’re tuned into it,  you know it’s not a voice to ignore. It’s taking you on a path that’s more suited to your dreams, more in tune with your purpose and offering you a ride that’s similar to a tube run down your favourite mountain river in summer – shaded by palm trees, and enough rapids for a bit of squealing fun, but not enough to tip you out and spill your glass of wine.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>156</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:44:06</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:44:06</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>why-you-should-listen-to-your-inner-voice</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[197]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:comment>
			<wp:comment_id>3</wp:comment_id>
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[themeparadise]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email>theme.paradise14@gmail.com</wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_author_IP>219.92.146.1</wp:comment_author_IP>
			<wp:comment_date>2015-09-16 14:10:09</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>2015-09-16 14:10:09</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[You should listen to your inner voice! Listen]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
			<wp:comment_user_id>3</wp:comment_user_id>
			<wp:commentmeta>
				<wp:meta_key>akismet_error</wp:meta_key>
				<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1442412609]]></wp:meta_value>
			</wp:commentmeta>
			<wp:commentmeta>
				<wp:meta_key>akismet_history</wp:meta_key>
				<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:4:{s:4:"time";d:1442412609.0896270275115966796875;s:5:"event";s:11:"check-error";s:4:"user";s:13:"themeparadise";s:4:"meta";a:1:{s:8:"response";s:7:"invalid";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
			</wp:commentmeta>
		</wp:comment>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Steve Jobs</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/08/15/steve-jobs/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 01:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=158</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Your time is precious, so don’t waste it living someone else’s life]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>158</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-08-15 01:46:44</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-08-15 01:46:44</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>steve-jobs</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="quotes"><![CDATA[Quotes]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[in-defense-of-the-pageant]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Do you workout while you are on vacation?</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/do-you-workout-while-you-are-on-vacation/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=160</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Nulla sit amet porta risus. Donec nec lorem non arcu facilisis posuere. Vivamus vulputate et massa non pretium. Vivamus fringilla lacinia erat, sit amet iaculis metus. Donec augue turpis, ultricies quis lorem et, egestas convallis nibh. Morbi magna tortor, suscipit quis placerat nec, posuere nec odio. Aliquam erat volutpat. Aliquam id tellus et quam ultricies pharetra. Integer id tempor purus, et maximus orci. Pellentesque dapibus finibus ex in consequat. Vestibulum eget velit commodo, sagittis sapien in, feugiat nisi. Aliquam feugiat dui massa, egestas mollis orci maximus varius. Phasellus purus sapien, eleifend nec efficitur at, rutrum eu sem.

Vestibulum ut elit mauris. Aenean ut diam ornare, rhoncus leo eget, dictum tortor. Suspendisse eu lobortis lacus. Suspendisse tincidunt lectus vel ipsum vehicula tristique. Vestibulum in auctor nisl. Morbi tincidunt ante nec nisl aliquet consectetur. Pellentesque enim libero, eleifend vel eros eget, interdum vulputate quam. Mauris efficitur nulla lacus, et viverra sem sagittis luctus.

Cras tristique gravida quam, eget pellentesque libero. Duis arcu nibh, fringilla eu sollicitudin ut, placerat non nunc. Integer risus nisl, dictum ut porttitor vel, laoreet vel nunc. Nam vel ultrices nisl. Etiam nisi mi, egestas quis ipsum quis, convallis sodales elit. Nullam porttitor faucibus velit, sed pretium sapien cursus quis. Nam viverra, turpis ut ullamcorper convallis, dui ipsum luctus mi, in fringilla nisi lorem ut diam. Donec turpis sapien, iaculis in nulla non, malesuada pretium libero. Curabitur a arcu malesuada, porttitor elit vel, sodales nisl. Nunc pulvinar eleifend congue. Proin eget dui cursus, placerat tortor a, consectetur arcu. Quisque enim sem, accumsan eu risus ultricies, mattis interdum mi. Aliquam condimentum dolor sed ante bibendum, sed aliquam felis venenatis. Vivamus maximus lectus odio, eget interdum enim ornare vel.

Suspendisse accumsan metus at lacinia dignissim. Vestibulum nec tristique ex. Cras elit massa, fermentum eu cursus sit amet, dignissim nec nisl. Integer hendrerit iaculis ipsum ac efficitur. Phasellus commodo velit sit amet nunc commodo, vitae bibendum lorem hendrerit. Nunc pretium justo eget imperdiet lobortis. Nunc aliquam orci sit amet ex convallis, at sollicitudin dui imperdiet. Ut porta libero et consequat auctor. Cras laoreet, nisl quis interdum lobortis, neque leo commodo odio, vitae consequat tortor erat ac turpis. Donec sit amet lobortis dui, in venenatis diam. Fusce vitae velit sed sapien dictum imperdiet in ac nisl. Phasellus ac risus vitae sapien ultricies sagittis ac non felis. Integer tempor sodales imperdiet. Vestibulum nec condimentum ex. Pellentesque porta mollis ex, a volutpat felis tincidunt eget.

Suspendisse vitae dignissim tortor. In lobortis condimentum magna dapibus molestie. Vestibulum vestibulum sapien id arcu egestas, eu gravida mauris gravida. Integer at gravida nibh. Mauris tempor tortor ac pretium suscipit. Fusce aliquet ligula at vestibulum sagittis. Mauris in metus id ipsum suscipit faucibus. Maecenas imperdiet, dolor nec sodales congue, odio quam finibus lacus, nec tempor felis nunc at mi. Fusce et aliquam leo, scelerisque convallis nulla.

Nunc elementum odio dui, et eleifend arcu interdum pulvinar. Donec pulvinar, lectus id ultricies venenatis, nunc diam blandit justo, vitae sollicitudin ligula magna id nibh. Fusce scelerisque eros mollis, sagittis enim in, rhoncus quam. Donec lobortis consequat tristique. Etiam nec tincidunt nibh, vitae commodo enim. Aliquam auctor lectus leo, eget placerat sapien accumsan ut. Pellentesque tortor velit, gravida nec aliquet sed, egestas non urna. Donec auctor varius mollis. Quisque et dictum ligula, eget molestie nisi. Nunc feugiat tellus vitae mi vulputate pretium. Pellentesque gravida venenatis risus, eu sodales lacus dapibus in. Etiam varius, arcu sit amet suscipit rhoncus, nunc tortor lobortis nibh, at imperdiet dolor ipsum eu dolor. Vivamus mollis sapien facilisis felis cursus, ac euismod eros sodales. Ut id tempor mi. Sed et augue ligula. Phasellus elementum mattis felis nec ultricies.

Integer ut neque sit amet nisi bibendum dictum. Integer condimentum, leo sit amet maximus tincidunt, mauris massa dapibus libero, a porttitor purus ex et nisi. Etiam egestas orci et interdum cursus. Morbi in gravida lectus, quis eleifend arcu. Pellentesque placerat tincidunt blandit. In ac mauris ut ipsum pulvinar consequat. Duis dignissim posuere ligula, vel iaculis nulla pharetra sed. Proin sapien leo, volutpat ac ipsum vel, aliquet tincidunt nulla. Vivamus augue erat, dapibus sed nisi vitae, sagittis placerat mauris. Maecenas et est lobortis, bibendum arcu sed, ullamcorper massa. Sed non ipsum imperdiet justo gravida hendrerit vel et ipsum.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>160</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:49:45</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:49:45</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>do-you-workout-while-you-are-on-vacation</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sports"><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[275]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[nobody-wants-to-go-to-the-us-open-anymore-now-that-serena-is-out]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Designers are using tech to break fashion week rules and we like it</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/designers-are-using-tech-to-break-fashion-week-rules-and-we-like-it/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=162</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Donec elementum diam quis tellus tincidunt sagittis. Ut et placerat urna. Vestibulum vitae felis gravida, pretium magna sit amet, aliquet risus. Curabitur hendrerit sem ullamcorper, sodales felis et, ultrices justo. Ut venenatis enim sed lacus tempor, ut rutrum ante pharetra. Sed sodales laoreet justo et auctor. Mauris ullamcorper non ante vitae cursus. Etiam placerat metus vitae erat vehicula convallis. Etiam scelerisque ligula ut lorem consequat rutrum. Cras sed ornare ligula, ac tincidunt nulla. In dictum odio vitae varius dignissim. Morbi elementum erat ut mattis imperdiet. Maecenas ut varius velit. Nulla quis viverra nunc. Aenean efficitur metus nibh, at dignissim purus fermentum in. Integer mattis cursus mauris, sed placerat odio feugiat et.

Praesent egestas aliquet blandit. Nam facilisis mattis quam, quis malesuada mi tristique ut. Donec finibus condimentum scelerisque. Nullam sit amet fringilla leo. Mauris aliquet vehicula imperdiet. Suspendisse tortor dui, pulvinar sit amet purus sed, vulputate vulputate nisi. Nulla id sollicitudin ante. Sed id ante aliquam, vestibulum nisl ac, pulvinar dolor. Nam varius massa at gravida molestie. Donec pharetra tortor nec mollis vestibulum. Aenean posuere tempus mauris nec pulvinar. Phasellus gravida feugiat tortor, eu iaculis orci auctor quis. Donec semper suscipit lobortis. Aliquam vitae mi lorem. Proin semper ipsum dolor, non venenatis est aliquam sodales.

Integer faucibus vestibulum sem non suscipit. Integer eu tellus sit amet sapien auctor pellentesque ut et ipsum. Nunc luctus elit id nibh aliquam eleifend. Etiam dictum lectus nisi, a bibendum orci laoreet in. Nullam ullamcorper in sapien accumsan malesuada. Nam nisi diam, placerat vel cursus vel, ornare nec nunc. Integer ut arcu aliquet ex molestie vulputate id vestibulum libero. Sed dapibus sapien non sapien facilisis, vitae hendrerit ex vehicula. Integer nisi diam, lacinia in eleifend eget, rutrum eu justo. Donec sit amet tellus a diam placerat dignissim eget a nulla. Donec egestas libero sed dui facilisis, eget mattis nisi mattis. Cras ligula elit, auctor at lacus quis, placerat feugiat ex. Donec feugiat efficitur dapibus. Donec purus eros, eleifend imperdiet sem id, fermentum pharetra enim. Aenean quam massa, scelerisque sit amet leo sit amet, rutrum faucibus tortor.

Proin ut porttitor ex. In mollis scelerisque risus, id suscipit tellus varius pulvinar. Morbi cursus eget augue sit amet placerat. Pellentesque quis cursus dolor. Suspendisse iaculis dictum scelerisque. Ut non fermentum turpis, vel ornare dui. Praesent nec venenatis risus. Mauris lacus ante, rutrum ac augue id, convallis sagittis massa. Integer maximus dui sed orci varius, eget feugiat leo consequat. Pellentesque sodales diam ex, ac convallis velit vulputate non. Sed blandit tincidunt posuere. Maecenas tempus viverra eros ut eleifend. Sed viverra consectetur sagittis. Morbi faucibus, lorem a pellentesque scelerisque, lacus nunc tempus ex, eu cursus nibh tortor sed ex. Vivamus ante odio, accumsan rhoncus gravida ut, iaculis et massa. Quisque efficitur libero a aliquet malesuada.

Nam eget magna eget nunc dignissim feugiat. Nam non justo a diam scelerisque accumsan. Suspendisse tincidunt libero non vestibulum mattis. In porta et odio vel mattis. Vestibulum rhoncus interdum tempor. Mauris tempus semper tristique. Integer metus ex, ullamcorper vitae consectetur id, semper ac nibh. Praesent dictum tortor sagittis diam sollicitudin, ut lacinia leo laoreet.

Aenean in dolor velit. Ut ut neque sed velit rhoncus aliquam in ac massa. Nunc eu imperdiet quam. Nullam eleifend sapien sit amet molestie interdum. Nullam mattis lacinia pretium. Maecenas varius ligula urna. Cras et augue ipsum.

Vivamus urna nulla, pellentesque eget dolor at, aliquet luctus turpis. Praesent quis odio in tellus accumsan sagittis sed at est. Suspendisse facilisis non arcu sit amet bibendum. Maecenas dapibus congue velit. Ut quis accumsan ligula, ac placerat velit. Duis eros ligula, vulputate sed nibh nec, pulvinar fermentum lacus. Vestibulum pretium porta nisi. Vestibulum justo nulla, dapibus vitae est eu, hendrerit iaculis velit. In placerat, ipsum sed condimentum commodo, est lorem vulputate sapien, vitae iaculis enim arcu eget augue. Morbi laoreet vitae turpis et ullamcorper. Donec viverra, orci at scelerisque venenatis, eros tellus finibus ligula, et ornare tortor felis et nibh. Phasellus eget rhoncus justo. Interdum et malesuada fames ac ante ipsum primis in faucibus.

Sed molestie diam id nunc vehicula porttitor. Quisque sed dapibus risus. Sed ac tincidunt augue. Sed viverra quam nibh, sed feugiat nisi condimentum et. Fusce sagittis maximus lacus vitae fermentum. Aliquam accumsan mattis vehicula. Nam eu orci sagittis, pulvinar lacus in, interdum sem. Fusce vulputate ac elit vitae faucibus. Vivamus finibus fermentum eros, eget porta odio pulvinar placerat. Vivamus eget laoreet arcu. Cras auctor lectus sagittis justo dapibus, eu congue sem vulputate.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>162</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:50:55</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:50:55</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>designers-are-using-tech-to-break-fashion-week-rules-and-we-like-it</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>1</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[192]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_is_featured</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>&#039;Drunk History&#039; newlyweds dazzle with spellbinding first dance</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/drunk-history-newlyweds-dazzle-with-spellbinding-first-dance/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=164</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Vivamus urna nulla, pellentesque eget dolor at, aliquet luctus turpis. Praesent quis odio in tellus accumsan sagittis sed at est. Suspendisse facilisis non arcu sit amet bibendum. Maecenas dapibus congue velit. Ut quis accumsan ligula, ac placerat velit. Duis eros ligula, vulputate sed nibh nec, pulvinar fermentum lacus. Vestibulum pretium porta nisi. Vestibulum justo nulla, dapibus vitae est eu, hendrerit iaculis velit. In placerat, ipsum sed condimentum commodo, est lorem vulputate sapien, vitae iaculis enim arcu eget augue. Morbi laoreet vitae turpis et ullamcorper. Donec viverra, orci at scelerisque venenatis, eros tellus finibus ligula, et ornare tortor felis et nibh. Phasellus eget rhoncus justo. Interdum et malesuada fames ac ante ipsum primis in faucibus.

Sed molestie diam id nunc vehicula porttitor. Quisque sed dapibus risus. Sed ac tincidunt augue. Sed viverra quam nibh, sed feugiat nisi condimentum et. Fusce sagittis maximus lacus vitae fermentum. Aliquam accumsan mattis vehicula. Nam eu orci sagittis, pulvinar lacus in, interdum sem. Fusce vulputate ac elit vitae faucibus. Vivamus finibus fermentum eros, eget porta odio pulvinar placerat. Vivamus eget laoreet arcu. Cras auctor lectus sagittis justo dapibus, eu congue sem vulputate.

Nam facilisis, tortor porttitor aliquet laoreet, risus lorem consequat augue, id vehicula erat metus ut tellus. In consectetur, sem accumsan pulvinar pulvinar, augue purus bibendum quam, posuere laoreet sem orci non lectus. Donec dignissim malesuada imperdiet. Sed vitae mi dolor. Aliquam ut tortor nec orci efficitur consectetur nec vehicula turpis. Fusce porta in lacus et ultrices. Aenean eleifend id diam id scelerisque. Praesent et est eu felis viverra condimentum vel sit amet ex. Suspendisse ac tempus est. Proin pretium hendrerit dictum. Curabitur eros orci, luctus in ex at, tincidunt volutpat elit. Fusce non pretium nunc. Phasellus pulvinar ipsum quis blandit pulvinar. Mauris imperdiet sit amet mauris in viverra. Aenean ornare, velit nec tincidunt blandit, diam augue varius nisl, ut porta massa ante vitae odio. Vestibulum eleifend hendrerit cursus.

Sed feugiat lacinia congue. Fusce eget elit ornare, fermentum enim non, fringilla velit. Praesent hendrerit pulvinar varius. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Maecenas tristique gravida nisl, dictum porttitor augue fermentum quis. Proin consectetur dui lorem. Cras ullamcorper ex eget lorem porttitor pharetra. Phasellus quam nibh, tincidunt quis tellus in, molestie egestas leo. Donec vehicula turpis hendrerit lacinia molestie. Maecenas mollis mi fringilla congue sagittis.

Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Cras eleifend urna ut felis porta rhoncus. Integer vitae consequat velit. Aliquam erat volutpat. Nam fringilla augue massa, a condimentum diam rhoncus eget. Proin vel metus sodales, consectetur purus in, dignissim massa. Pellentesque ut lacus erat. Cras sed varius ligula, in malesuada massa. Sed ut dolor vel augue gravida laoreet. Vestibulum a ante id augue porta porta. Vestibulum lobortis augue tristique massa fringilla lobortis non ac diam. Donec porttitor dapibus convallis.

Sed aliquam lacus at justo sagittis fermentum. Curabitur tempus sem id lectus mollis dignissim. Nulla vestibulum viverra quam, at tincidunt eros dictum at. Sed lacinia, lorem ac vulputate ultrices, dui nulla mollis nunc, in iaculis mi tellus a sem. Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia Curae; Integer auctor tristique vulputate. Donec eu quam non felis pharetra mattis vel quis lacus. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.

Sed tincidunt purus vestibulum dui congue hendrerit. Aliquam consectetur mauris vitae enim mollis iaculis. Aenean et euismod ante. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Integer ante leo, ullamcorper condimentum sollicitudin quis, mollis vel enim. Praesent nulla lorem, eleifend a facilisis vel, molestie vitae tellus. Ut tincidunt lectus et magna mattis mollis. Ut molestie justo ante, at pulvinar diam interdum eu. Praesent nibh tortor, volutpat quis elit et, congue varius nulla. In consectetur pharetra magna. Donec eros neque, euismod nec ultricies et, convallis vitae quam. Quisque luctus ac sem vitae egestas.

Proin sollicitudin leo ac consequat elementum. Fusce vehicula tristique aliquet. In elementum diam sed eros tempus, nec facilisis mi tincidunt. Quisque velit justo, lacinia sed orci sed, dapibus cursus ante. Ut sollicitudin libero a malesuada congue. Etiam a ex ex. Praesent mauris urna, ornare nec enim quis, varius finibus quam. Donec id tortor ac nibh facilisis facilisis. Morbi eget faucibus libero. Duis nec libero ultricies, dictum dui in, ultricies lectus.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>164</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:52:43</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:52:43</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>drunk-history-newlyweds-dazzle-with-spellbinding-first-dance</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[195]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>7 Ways to relax &#038; be romantic</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/7-ways-to-relax-be-romantic/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=166</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[When we found out we were going to the Barossa Valley as a couple after 18 months traveling around Australia in a camper trailer with our kids, we were excited.

Finally a chance for relaxation and a little romance. What’s that again?

We’ve already shared with you the natural beauty of this region and the incredible food and wine you can have. Now let’s talk about how to unwind and fall in love.

There’s a lot of love floating around in the Barossa air. It can be felt in every conversation, every morsel of food that is grown and eaten, the stories that stand behind everything that is produced, and with every sweet, dry, rich and flavoursome bottle of wine.

We were invited as guests of Jacob’s Creek to experience what their wine is #MadeBy. It all comes back to love, passion and connectedness and that’s always how you shape the most miraculous things.

Let’s see how you can get your Marvin Gaye on and experience more of that in the Barossa and Adelaide Hills.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>166</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:53:50</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:53:50</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>7-ways-to-relax-be-romantic</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[194]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[7-ways-to-relax-be-romantic-in-barossa-valley-adelaide-hills]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Apple might finally let you delete those pre-installed apps you don&#039;t want</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/09/14/apple-might-finally-let-you-delete-those-pre-installed-apps-you-dont-want/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 01:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.120/semona/old-blog/?p=168</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[It's about time, Apple.

The company is considering allowing users to remove certain apps that come — and stay — pre-installed with iOS.

Apple CEO Tim Cook said the company is "looking at" ways to allow people to remove some of the apps that come on iPhones and iPads, he told BuzzFeed.

When asked about those apps — commonly referred to as "bloatware" — Cook chose his words carefully, though acknowledged that "some people" may wish to remove the applications.

“This is a more complex issue than it first appears,” he said. “There are some apps that are linked to something else on the iPhone. If they were to be removed they might cause issues elsewhere on the phone. There are other apps that aren’t like that. So over time, I think with the ones that aren’t like that, we’ll figure out a way [for you to remove them]. … It’s not that we want to suck up your real estate; we’re not motivated to do that. We want you to be happy. So I recognize that some people want to do this, and it’s something we’re looking at.”

Cook appears to make a distinction between core iOS apps — like Mail, Safari, Camera and the App Store — and ones like Compass, Stocks and Tips, which don't play a significant role in iOS as a whole and don't have much of an impact other apps. It seems that the company is considering allowing users to remove apps from this latter group. (Tips was new in iOS 8, but Stocks and Compass came in earlier iterations.)

While you'll probably be stuck with the iOS Mail app as your default email app until the end of iPhone time, you may finally be able to delete the Stocks, Tips and Compass apps. It's not clear when, or even if, this might happen, but the mere fact that Apple is considering it is news that we welcome with open arms.

Have something to add to this story? Share it in the comments.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>168</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-09-14 01:56:05</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-09-14 01:56:05</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>apple-might-finally-let-you-delete-those-pre-installed-apps-you-dont-want</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="technology"><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[193]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[getaway-to-great-keppel-island-in-queensland]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Amazing Audio Post</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/08/14/amazing-audio-post/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 12:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-paradise.com/semona/simple-blog/?p=179</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Fusce convallis metus id felis luctus adipiscing. Pellentesque egestas, neque sit amet convallis pulvinar, justo nulla eleifend augue, ac auctor orci leo non est. Quisque id mi. Ut tincidunt tincidunt erat. Etiam feugiat lorem non metus. Vestibulum dapibus nunc ac augue. Curabitur vestibulum aliquam leo. Praesent egestas neque eu enim. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Fusce a quam. Etiam ut purus mattis mauris sodales aliquam. Curabitur nisi. Quisque malesuada placerat nisl. Nam ipsum risus, rutrum vitae, vestibulum eu, molestie vel, lacus.
<blockquote>Sed augue ipsum, egestas nec, vestibulum et, malesuada adipiscing, dui. Vestibulum facilisis, purus nec pulvinar iaculis, ligula mi congue nunc, vitae euismod ligula urna in dolor. Mauris sollicitudin fermentum libero. Praesent nonummy mi in odio. Nunc interdum lacus sit amet orci.</blockquote>
Vestibulum rutrum, mi nec elementum vehicula, eros quam gravida nisl, id fringilla neque ante vel mi. Morbi mollis tellus ac sapien. Phasellus volutpat, metus eget egestas mollis, lacus lacus blandit dui, id egestas quam mauris ut lacus. Fusce vel dui. Sed in libero ut nibh placerat accumsan. Proin faucibus arcu quis ante. In consectetuer turpis ut velit. Nulla sit amet est.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>179</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-08-14 12:45:55</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-08-14 12:45:55</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>amazing-audio-post</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[url]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[http://demo.theme-paradise.com/videos/sample.mp3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Nice Video Post</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/08/14/nice-video-post/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 12:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-paradise.com/semona/simple-blog/?p=181</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Praesent vestibulum dapibus nibh. Etiam iaculis nunc ac metus. Ut id nisl quis enim dignissim sagittis. Etiam sollicitudin, ipsum eu pulvinar rutrum, tellus ipsum laoreet sapien, quis venenatis ante odio sit amet eros. Proin magna. Duis vel nibh at velit scelerisque suscipit. Curabitur turpis. Vestibulum suscipit nulla quis orci. Fusce ac felis sit amet ligula pharetra condimentum. Maecenas egestas arcu quis ligula mattis placerat. Duis lobortis massa imperdiet quam. Suspendisse potenti.
<blockquote>Class aptent taciti sociosqu ad litora torquent per conubia nostra, per inceptos hymenaeos. Pellentesque commodo eros a enim. Vestibulum turpis sem, aliquet eget, lobortis pellentesque, rutrum eu, nisl.</blockquote>
Sed libero. Aliquam erat volutpat. Etiam vitae tortor. Morbi vestibulum volutpat enim. Aliquam eu nunc. Nunc sed turpis. Sed mollis, eros et ultrices tempus, mauris ipsum aliquam libero, non adipiscing dolor urna a orci. Nulla porta dolor.
<blockquote>Pellentesque dapibus hendrerit tortor. Praesent egestas tristique nibh. Sed a libero. Cras varius. Donec vitae orci sed dolor rutrum auctor. Fusce egestas elit eget lorem. Suspendisse nisl elit, rhoncus eget, elementum ac, condimentum eget, diam.</blockquote>
Nam at tortor in tellus interdum sagittis. Aliquam lobortis. Donec orci lectus, aliquam ut, faucibus non, euismod id, nulla. Curabitur blandit mollis lacus. Nam adipiscing. Vestibulum eu odio.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>181</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-08-14 12:46:42</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-08-14 12:46:42</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>nice-video-post</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[url]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[http://demo.theme-paradise.com/videos/lake_time_lapse.mp4]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Embedded Video Post</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/08/14/embedded-video-post/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 12:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-paradise.com/semona/simple-blog/?p=183</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Duis leo. Sed fringilla mauris sit amet nibh. Donec sodales sagittis magna. Sed consequat, leo eget bibendum sodales, augue velit cursus nunc, quis gravida magna mi a libero. Fusce vulputate eleifend sapien. Vestibulum purus quam, scelerisque ut, mollis sed, nonummy id, metus. Nullam accumsan lorem in dui. Cras ultricies mi eu turpis hendrerit fringilla. Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia Curae; In ac dui quis mi consectetuer lacinia.
<blockquote class="alt">Donec sodales sagittis magna. Sed consequat, leo eget bibendum sodales, augue velit cursus nunc, quis gravida magna mi a libero. Fusce vulputate eleifend sapien. Nam pretium turpis et arcu. Duis arcu tortor, suscipit eget, imperdiet nec, imperdiet iaculis, ipsum.</blockquote>
Sed aliquam ultrices mauris. Integer ante arcu, accumsan a, consectetuer eget, posuere ut, mauris. Praesent adipiscing. Phasellus ullamcorper ipsum rutrum nunc. Nunc nonummy metus. Vestibulum volutpat pretium libero. Cras id dui. Aenean ut eros et nisl sagittis vestibulum. Nullam nulla eros, ultricies sit amet, nonummy id, imperdiet feugiat, pede. Sed lectus. Donec mollis hendrerit risus. Phasellus nec sem in justo pellentesque facilisis. Etiam imperdiet imperdiet orci. Nunc nec neque. Phasellus leo dolor, tempus non, auctor et, hendrerit quis, nisi.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>183</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-08-14 12:47:29</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-08-14 12:47:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>embedded-video-post</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="nature"><![CDATA[Nature]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7GIsNkPNcW4"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed-video-post]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Embedded Audio Post</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/08/14/embedded-audio-post/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 12:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-paradise.com/semona/simple-blog/?p=185</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Amazing Embedded Audio Post]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>185</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-08-14 12:48:34</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-08-14 12:48:34</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>embedded-audio-post</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_old_slug</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed-audio-post]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<iframe width="100%" height="450" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/203112765&amp;auto_play=false&amp;hide_related=false&amp;show_comments=true&amp;show_user=true&amp;show_reposts=false&amp;visual=true"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>slide_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>This is password protected post</title>
		<link>http://blogs.semona.wpengine.com/2015/08/14/this-is-password-protected-post/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 13:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[semona]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-paradise.com/semona/simple-blog/?p=190</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[This content should not be visible until user inputs correct password]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>190</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-08-14 13:17:09</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-08-14 13:17:09</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>this-is-password-protected-post</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password>password</wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>fg_temp_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;s:1:"0";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2_replacement</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>sbg_selected_sidebar_2</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_vc_post_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:2:{s:7:"vc_grid";a:0:{}s:10:"vc_grid_id";a:0:{}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[embed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_featured_media_url</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_related_posts</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_show_comments</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_transparent_header_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_top_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_topbar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_topbar_bottom_border</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_main_nav_hover_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_header_v2_stretch</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_titlebar_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_layerslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_revslider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_custom_slider</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[below]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[none]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_slider_decoration_skin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[light]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_display_footer</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_style</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_display_bar</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[yes]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bar_shortcode</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_footer_bg_image_opacity</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_sidebar_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_color</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_type</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_pattern</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_image</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_outer_bg_repeat</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_top</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>crf_content_padding_bottom</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
